(Sheldon:)Look, I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)Tell me why
Bernadette is upset with you.
(Penny:)Well, I told people at work
that she's pregnant.
(Penny:)She wasn't ready
for them to know.
(Sheldon:)Why would you do that?
(Penny:)Well, it just slipped out.
I feel terrible.
(Sheldon:)See, that's exactly
what happened to me,
(Sheldon:)except that I said it on
purpose, and I have no regrets.
(Raj:)Is it even possible
to get this done in two months?
(Howard:)Well, maybe. I don't know.
We'll have to work
(Howard:)12 hours a day,
seven days a week.
(Leonard:)Which means I won't be able to
make Penny breakfast every day,
(Leonard:)and she'll realize
my brioche French toast
(Leonard:)was the only thing
keeping her in the marriage.
(Howard:)I love your
French toast.
(Leonard:)Oh, thanks, man.
(Raj:)So, why did you guys
even agree to the deadline?
(Howard:)We didn't. Sheldon did.
(Raj:)And you just let him?
(Leonard:)Well, the colonel said it was
for the good of the country,
(Leonard:)and the funding
is substantial.
(Howard:)No, but mostly, there
was an awkward pause,
(Howard:)and I broke it
by saying, "Okay."
(Raj:)So I guess I won't be
seeing you guys for a while.
(Leonard:)Oh, looks like it.
(Raj:)Wow.
(Raj:)You're going off to work with
the military, leaving me behind.